Finding Aid for the Edwin Mims Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Edwin Mims Papers
multiple
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0292
10.49 linear_feet
- Series I
  - Correspondence - Incoming (Box 1 - 2)
    Incoming correspondence of 923 letters, 16 cards, 2 telegrams. Alphabetically arranged.
  - Correspondence - Incoming. Alphabetically arranged. (Box 3)
    Correspondence - Outgoing. Chronologically arranged. Miscellaneous letters. Letters with incomplete and illegible signatures. Outgoing correspondence (xerox copies), 1902-59 (62 letters).
  - Autobiographical and biographical material. Class notes and lectures. (Box 4)
  - Bound volume of tributes to Edwin Mims on the occasion of his retirement. 2 scrapbooks (1894 - 1951) of, by, or of interest to Mims. (Box 5)
  - Manuscripts: Lee's Life after the Civil War: History of Vanderbilt Adventurous America Eyes that Saw Chancellor Kirkland. (Box 6)
  - Addresses. Printed Material. (Box 7)
  - Research notes. (Box 8)
  - Research notes. (Box 9)
  - Report and discussion of faculty committee on schedules and courses of study. Book reviews. Papers of Southern Education Association and General Education Board. Micellaneous. Scrapbooks., Location: M/2/15 (Box 10)
  - Addendum:
    - Microfilm of unpublished manuscript, To Seek a Newer World: The Selected Correspondence of Edwin Mims. Michael O'Brien, ed. 866 frames. (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, outgoing - letters to Clara (Puryear) Mims, arranged chronologically. (Box 11 - 15)
    - Letters to C.P.M. from others, alpha. arranged; Letters to E.M. from C.P.M., chronologically arranged; Correspondence, outgoing - general, chronologically arranged; Correspondence, incoming, alpha. arranged, A - M. (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, incoming, N - Y, plus fragments, first names only, and illegibles; Correspondence - miscellaneous (between others) (Box 16)
    - Mtl. other than correspondence is arranged alphabetically in boxes 15 - 22.
    - "Ad" (Box 16)
      Addresses- Mss.; Addresses, misc., untitled and extracts; The Advancing South - advertisements, etc.; Adventurous America - comments on.
    - "Al - Au" (Box 17)
      Dr. Alderman - Notes on; Articles, misc. published writings about Mims, arranged chronologically; Articles, miscellaneous published writings by Mims, arranged chronologically; Autobiography - "A Forward" - "The Grand Tour".
    - "Au - Cl" (Box 18)
      Autobiography - "A Bright Interval" - "Terminus? No:"; Chancellor Kirkland of Vanderbilt - advertisements, reviews; Class lectures; Clippings, misc. published material collected by Mims, arranged chronologically.
    - "Co - Mss." (Box 19)
      Comments by others about Mims' lecture tours; French Diary; Lecture programs, course syllabus
      Mss. - "Anti-Lynching Movement" - "A Reconsideration of Early Southern Literature".
    - "Mss. - Misc. Ms. Mtl." (Box 20)
      Mss. - "The Romance and Realism of the West" - "The Voice of the Negro"
      Misc. lists and programs; Misc. ms. mtl., typed originals and carbons, autobiographical and ganeral
    - "Misc. Notes - Ph." (Box 21)
      Misc. notes, mss; Pamphlets; Passport, Photograph.
    - "Pu - T" (Box 22)
      Publisher's Mtls.; Research Notes; Scottish Diary; "The Southern Woman - Past and Present"; Travel accounts; Tributes and biographical mtl.
Index
This is a name index of the correspondents of Edwin Mims. The figure (or figures) in parentheses immediately following each name denotes the total number of letters from that person in the collection; the dates are for the time of the letters. The full name of the writer is given whenever possible; the last number given refers to the box in which the correspondence may be found.
- Abbott, Ernest Hamlin, (1), Dec. 30, 1903; 1
- Abbott, Lyman, (5), May 13, 1903, May 8, 1906, Feb. 18, Mar. 13, 21, 1907; 1
- Adams, Agnes, (3), Sept. 5, 1937, Jan. 20, Sept. 30, 1941; 1
- Adamson, Robert, (1), Dec. 16, 1926; 1
- Adgerlaw, Robert, (1 telegram)
- Aiken, Newton, (1), Mar. 29, 1956; 1
- Alderman, E. A., (9), Feb. 6, 1908, Nov. 24, 1911, Jan. 2, 1912, Feb. 26, Mar. 5, 1917, Aug. 16, 1922, Jan. 3, 1925, Dec. 6, 1929, Jan. 7, 1931; 1
- Alexander, carter, (1), Nov. 25, 1941; 1
- Alexander, Eben, (1), Sept. 1, 190?; 1
- Alexander, W. J., (1), Feb. 4, 1904; 1
- Alexander, Will W., (5), May 21, Nov. 5, 1926, Feb. 4, 27, 1927, April 10, 1931; 1
- Amis, Lewis R., (1), Mar. 3, 1941; 1
- Anderson, Charles, (1), Feb. 5, 1942; 1
- Anderson, James A., (1), July 14, 1913; 1
- Anderson, Wade H., (1), May 17, 1934; 1
- Angell, James R., 2 Nov. 4, 1926, June 20, 1930; 1
- Arnett, Trevor, (1), Dec. 27, 1940; 1
- Ashmore, Harry S., (1), Jan. 30, 1958; 1
- Aswell, Edward C., (1), Dec. 21, 1926; 1
- Aycock, C. B., (3), Oct. 1, 1903, Jan. 1, 1904, June 28, 1904; 1
- Aydelotte, Frank, (1), Sept. 17, 1937;1
- Babbitt, Irving, (1), Feb. 22, 1914; 1
- Bailey, J. W., (4), Nov. 15, 1905, Feb. 13, 1906, Dec. 21, 1908, Dec. 30, 1910; 1
- Baker, Ray Stannard, (2), June 11, Dec. 26, no year; 1
- Baldwin, W. H., Jr., (1), no date; 1
- Baskerville, W. M., (1), May 2, 1898; 1
- Bassett, John Spencer, (8), Oct. 23, 1906, Feb. 9, Oct. 17, Dec. 13, 1907, Jan. 1, Apr. 18, 1909, Sept. 4, 1910, Apr. 13, 1925; 1
- Bell, Maggie, (ltelegram), May 25, 1942; 1
- Bennett, John, (1), Oct. 28, 1908; 1
- Bester, Arthur, (2), Feb. 14, 1919, Aug. 13, 1929; 1
- Bingham, R., (1), May 27, 1907; 1
- Bingham, Robert W., (2), July 26, Oct. 1, 1937; 1
- Bishop, David H., (1), Apr. 7, 1941; 1
- Blackwall, R. E., (1), May 25, 1913; 1
- Blair, D. H., (1), June 29, 1928; 1
- Bonner, Campbell, (1), Feb. 5, 1940; 1
- Boynton, Percy H., (2), Mar. 13, 1916, Jan. 27, 1930,; 1
- Bradford, Gamaliel, (2), Dec. 1, 10, 1929; 1
- Bradley, Sculley, (1), Sept. 28, 1942; 1
- Branscomb, Harvie, (1), Oct. 5, 1946; 1
- Branson, E. C., (2), Jan. 9, 1906, June 11, 1926; 1
- Brie, F., (1), Jan. 25, 1930; 1
- Brierley, W. W., (1), Dec. 20, 1930; 1
- Brooks, Van Wyck, (7), Jan. 8, Mar. 28, 1942, May 1, June 5, 1953, Apr. 6, 1954, July 10, 1957, Feb. 2, 1958; 1
- Brown, Calvin S., (1), Sept. 15, 1943; 1
- Brown, Charles R., (1), Dec. 16, 1929; 1
- Brown, W. G., (6), Mar. 24, 1905, Jan. 16, Feb. 28, 1906, Apr. 20, 1907, 2 undated; 1
- Bryant, W. Alton, (1), May 19, 1942; 1
- Buck, Dudley, (2), Sept. 27, Oct. 2, 1904; 1
- Burton, Richard, (1), Dec. 16 no year; 1
- Butler, Nicholas M., (8), Jan. 12, 29, 1934, Oct. 17, Nov. 30, 1936, Dec. 7, 1937, Apr. 7, 1938, Nov. 27, 1939, Jan. 7, 1941; 1
- Buttrick, Wallace, (5), Feb. 23, Mar. 7, 1907, Jan. 25, 1911, May 8, 1926, Jan. 16, no year; 1
- Cadman, S. Parkes, (8), Oct. 20, 1925, Apr. 20, May 9, 20, 1926, Sept. 28, 1927, Jan. 11, 29, Dec. 28, 1929; 1
- Caldwell, J. P., (5), Nov. 11, 30, 1903, Oct. 29, 1907, July 9, Nov. 18, 1908; 1
- Caldwell, John T., (1), Mar. 15, 1955; 1
- Canby, Henry S., (1), Mar. 25, 1929; 1
- Carmichael, O. C., (1), Oct. 21, 1946; 1
- Carmichael, W. D., (1), Feb. 14, 1941; 1
- Carter, Hedding, (2), Feb. 7, 27, 1959; 1
- Cary, C. P., (1), Feb. 9, 1907; 1
- Cash, W. J., (1), Mar. 20, 1941; 1
- Challinor, Peggy, (1), May 26, 1936; 1
- Chandler, J. A.C., (1), Feb. 27, 1928; 1
- Chappell, J. E., (3), May 15, 20, 1926, June 2, 1926; 1
- Chase, H. W., (1), May 18, 1926; 1
- Chase, Mary Ellen, (1), Nov. 12, no year; 1
- Childers, James Saxon, (2), Nov. 19, 1941, Mar. 29, 1956; 1
- Clark, Iris Moore, (1 telegram), N.D.; 1
- Connelly, Willard, (1), Mar. 18, 1938; 1
- Connor, Henry G., (1), July 7, N.Y.; 1
- Cooper, Prentice, (1), Feb. 20, 1940; 1
- Couch, W. T., (1), Aug. 21, 1926; 1
- Courtney, William H., (1), May 23, 1942; 1
- Crawford, George G., (1), May 31, 1926; 1
- Creel, Dana S., (1), Mar. 17, 1955; 1
- Crothers, S.M., (1), Apr. 3, 1907; 1
- Cullen, Thomas S., (2), Sept. 9, 1940, Mar. 25, 1941; 1
- Cullom, M. M., (1), May 26, 1942; 1
- Cullom, Neil P., (1), Oct. 30, 1939; 1
- Curry, Katherine Worth, (1), June 6, 1942; 1
- Curry, W. C., (2), June 8, 1942, Aug. 9 N.Y.; 1
- Cutting, E. B., (1), Dec. 28, 1926; 1
- Dabney, Virginius, (1), May 27, 1949; 1
- Daley, Elsa McGill, (1), May 25, N.Y.; 1
- Daniels, Josephus, (1), May 25, 1926; 1
- Darrow, Whitney, (2), Nov. 4, Dec. 5, 1929; 1
- Davidson, Donald, (1), Sept. 9, 1958; 1
- Davidson, Eloise, (1), May 25, 1942; 1
- Davis, Jackson, (1), June 10, 1926; 1
- Davis, Norman H., (4), Nov. 2, 1916, June 1, 1926, Sept. 18, 27, 1937; 1
- Diehl, Charles E., (1), May 18, 1942; 1
- Dillard, J. H., (1), July 18, 1926,; 1
- Dodd, William E., (7), Nov. 23, 1903, June 27, Sept. 15, 1906, May 10, 1917, June 7, 1924, Feb. 14, Mar. 9, 1927; 1
- Donovan, H. L., (1), May 26, 1926; 1
- Duncan, E. D., (1), Aug. 25, 1942; 1
- DuPont, Jesse Ball, (1), Oct. 28, 1950; 1
- Edison, Nina M., (Mrs. Thomas A.), (1), Aug. 14, 1929; 1
- Edman, Irvin (E)?, (1), Mar. 4, 1930; 1
- Eidson, John O., (1), July 27, 1953; 1
- Eliot, Charles W., (1), Sept. 30, 1903; 1
- Everett, Edwin M., (1), Mar. 14, 1955; 1
- Few, W. P., (1), N.D.; 1
- Field, Frederica, (3), Dec. 22, 1931, Jan. 18, Feb. 3, 1932; 1
- Fite, Alex, (1), Apr. 10, 1941; 1
- Fleming, Walter L., (2), Jan. 29, 1903, Aug. 15, 1907; 1
- Flexner, Abraham, (3), Nov. 20, Dec. 27, 1940, Dec. 11, 1956; 1
- Floyd, John A., (1), N.D.; 1
- Foerster, Norman, (1), Dec. 2, 1929; 1
- Fosdick, Harry Emerson, (5), May 5, 1922, Jan. 5, 1925, Nov. 4, 1929, Feb. 6, 1930, May 26, 1952; 1
- Fosdick, Raymond B., (2), Apr. 17, 1956, Nov. 1, 1958; 1
- Fowler, Margaret B., (1), Dec. 5, 1929; 1
- Freeman, D. S., (3), June 4, 15, 1926, Aug. 12, 1926; 1
- Furness, Horace Howard, (1), N.Y. Nov. 3; 1
- Gardner, Moffett, (1), Jan. 10, 12, 24, 1952; 1
- Garland, Hamlin, (2), May 8, Sept. 7, N.Y.; 1
- Garrison, Francis J., (1), Aug. 20, Oct. 25, Dec. 11, 1903, Oct. 16, 1905, Jun29, 1906, Apr. 15, 1909; 1
- Gayley, c. M., Oct. 30, Dec. 3, 1924; 1
- Gildersleeve, Basil L., (1), Sept. 29, 1902, Nov. 5, 1904, Dec. 30, 1905, Oct. 26, 1907; 1
- Gilman, D. C., (7) (lcard), Oct. 20, 26, 1904, Nov. 14, 1905, Jan. 16, 1906, June 25, Oct. 27, Nov. 4, N.Y. Dec. 2.; 1
- Glasgow, Ellen, (1), June 12, 1910, July 1, 1925, Apr. 28, May 12, Dec. 30, 1926, Jan. 6, Mar. 25, 1931, Sept. 9, 1932, Oct. 22, 1934, Jan. 7, Feb. 12, July 31, Oct. 6, 1935, Mar. 28, Dec. 11, 1936, Feb. 25, 1937, Oct. 4, 1939, Dec. 19, 28, 1940, Jan. 3, July 4, Aug. 9, Sept. 26, Dec. 29, 1941, Mar. 1, 29, 1942, Oct. 10, 1943, 3 N.D.; 1
- Godding, Mrs. C. A., (co-signed by Mrs. J. G. Bowman) (1), May 26, 1942; 1
- Graham, Edward K., (7), Mar. 29, 1909, June 9, 1914, Feb. 20, 1918, Apr. 27, 1918, 3, N.D.; 1
- Graham, Frank P., (1), Mar. 4, 1947; 1
- Greenstreet, Ferris, (18) (lcard), Jan. 9, May, 17, 24, June 8, 15, 26, 29, 1905, July 14, 19, 28, Aug. 16, 25, Nov. 20, 1905, Feb. 16, Oct. 10, 1906, Oct. 8, 1907, July 15, 1913, July 15, 1926, Nov. 20. N.Y.; 1
- Greever, Garland, (7), June 29, 1908, Nov. 5, 1911, Feb. 19, Oct. 9, 1912, July 9, 1913, Aug. 8, 1926, Jan. 29, 1941; 1
- Gregg, Alan, (1), Mar. 9, 1941; 1
- Guerry, Alex, (3), Mar. 13, 1941, Oct. 28, 1946, N.D.; 1
- Gunsaulus, F. W., (1), Nov. 27, 1907; 1
- Gupton, William, (1), May 15, 1942; 1
- Hadley, Arthur, (1), Oct. 31, 1901; 1
- Haggard, Mrs. M. W. and Adelaide, (1 telegram), May 26, 1942; 1
- Hale, George Ellery, (1), Dec. 13, 1929; 1
- Hall, Fitzgerald, (1), May 28, 1942; 1
- Hall, Grover, (1), June 11, 1926; 1
- Hammond, Emily v., (1), 1929; 1
- Hanson, V. H., (1), May 31, 1926; 1
- Harris, A. M., (1), Dec. 30, 1940; 1
- Harris, Corra, (7) (1 card), Aug. 17, 1906, Jan. 2, Dec. 16, 1908, Sept. 6, 1912, Jan. 9, 1913, Sept. 18, 1914, Nov. 16, 1919, N.D.; 1
- Harris, J. C., (5), May 18, Aug. 29, Sept. 24, 28, 1926, N.D.; 1
- Harris, Seale, (1), Sept. 5, 1941; 1
- Harrison, W. G., (1), May 26, 1941; 1
- Haskell, Henrys., (6), Oct. 5, 15, 29, 1934, Oct. 28, 1937, Feb. 24, Mar. 30, 1939; 1
- Hawthorne, Julian, (1), Jan. 29, 1908; 1
- Hay, James, Jr., (1), May 22, 1926; 1
- Heath, D. C. and Co., (1), Oct. 20, 1904; 2
- Henderson, Archibald, (6), Mar. 1, 26, 1902, May 12, 25, 1926, Sept. 2, 1926, Dec. 17, 1946; 2
- Hendrick, Burton J., (3), Jan. 29, 1923, Jan. 12, 1928, Nov. 23, 1932; 2
- Henneman, John Bell, (2), Sept. 8, 1903, May 18, 1908; 2
- Henry, Robert S., (1), June 24, 1940; 2
- Hibbard, Addison, (1), May 15, 1926; 2
- Hill, Walter B., (1), Jan. 21, 1904; 2
- Hoffman, Ural L., (1), May 24, 1942; 2
- Holt, Hamilton, (1), Apr. 17, 1947; 2
- Hough, Lynn Harold, (1), Nov. 29, 1929; 2
- House, Robert B., (1), Jan. 7, 1947; 2
- Howard, Hubert J., (2), Nov. 10, 1936, Sept. 21, 1937; 2
- Howe, M. A. DeWolfe, (2), Jan. 24, 1906, Nov. 6, 1929; 2
- Howe, W. D., (1), Nov. 4, 1929; 2
- Hughes, Rupert, (1), May 15, 1940; 2
- Hulme, William H., (1), Mar. 24, 1912; 2
- Hunt, Alice, (1), Mar. 12, 1951; 2
- Hunt, T. W., (1), July 17, 1926; 2
- Hutchins, Robert M., (1), Oct. 24, 1929; 2
- Jack, Theodore H., (1), Jan. 9, 1941; 2
- Jackson, Mannie Baxter, (1), May 26, 1942; 2
- Jaffe, Louis I., (1), May 15, 1926; 2
- Jaques, Ernest J., (1), Jan. 20, 1941; 2
- Jewell, W. B., (1), May 13, 1942; 2
- Johnson, Alvin, (1), Mar. 12, 1951; 2
- Johnson, Elizabeth Cody, (1), May 29, 1942; 2
- Johnson, Gerald W., (1), May 17, 1926; 2
- Jones, Howard M., (1), July 21, 1929; 2
- Judy, Clinton, (1), Apr. 11, 1941; 2
- Keeble, Edwin A., (1), Dec. 16, 1953; 2
- Kent, Charles W., (2), July 31, Dec. 4, 1907; 2
- Kern, Paul B., (1), Oct. 22, 1946; 2
- Ketcham Marion C., (1), Apr. 13, 1940; 2
- Kilgo, John C., (2), Mar. 12, 1899, July 6, 1908; 2
- King, Morton, (1), July 13, 1947; 2
- Kirkland, J. H., (24), June 23, Aug. 21, 1906, Mar. 25, 1909, Oct. 12 Dec. 31, 1910, Jan. 7, 16, 22, 26, 1911, Apr. 10, 1911, Jan. 12, 19, Feb. 3, 15, 21, Mar. 6, 8, 20, Apr. 16, 1912, Mar. 5, 1917, Dec. 26, 1930, June 26, 1933, June 5, 1937, May 12, N.Y.; 2
- Kirkland, Mary H. (1), N. D.; 2
- Kittredge, G. L., (1), May 9, 1911; 2
- Knickerbocker, (1), Nov. 3, 1929; 2
- Knight, Edgar W., (1), Sept. 15, 1926; 2
- Kodama, Kun, (1), June 7, 1950; 2
- Lake, Devereux, (1), Mar. 13, 1955; 2
- Lambeth, W. A., (1), July 14, 1905; 2
- Lanier, Charles D., (2), Nov. 4, 1904, Nov. 13, 1905; 2
- Lanier, Mrs. Clifford, (1), Nov. 12, 1905; 2
- Lanier, Henry W., (6), July 28, Aug. 3, Sept. 29, 1903, July 19, 1904, May 22, Nov. 9, 1905
- Lanier, Mary Day (Mrs. Sidney), (15) (8 cards), Oct. 12, 19, Nov. 22, Dec. 20, 1903, Mar. 15, July 8, Sept. 1, Dec. 15 (c), 21 (c), 30 (c), 1904, Jan. 2 (c), 4 (c), 14, 18, 28 (c), Feb. 10, Mar. 2, July 20, 1905, Jan. 25, May 31, June 1 (c), 1907, Jan. 28, N.Y.; 2
- Lanier, May Field, (2), N.D.; 2
- Latane, John H., (1), Jan. 27, 1905; 2
- Leathers, W. S., (2), Dec. 8, 1939, May 27, 1942; 2
- Lee Ivy, (2), Jan. 1, 14, 1930; 2
- Levy, Jean Weinstein, (lcard), N.D.; 2
- Lewis, Nell Battle, (1), May 14, 1926; 2
- Longwell, Daniel, (7), Apr. 29, May 12, 18, 25, 28, June 8, 15, 1926; 2
- Loveman, Amy, (1), Oct. 21, 1929; 2
- Lowes, John Livingston, (1), Jan. 15, 1930; 2
- Lyles, Adlai, (1), June 4, 1942; 2
- Mabie, Hamilton W., (14), Nov. 14, 1902, Jan. 31, Nov. 5, Dec. 5, 1905, Jan. 3, 23, May 6, Oct. 8, 19, 1906, Feb. 18, Nov. 27, 1907, Jan. 18, 1908, Oct. 11, 1910, N.D.; 2
- McBride, John M., (3), Jan. 2, 13, 1925, Mar. 10, 1927; 2
- McCarty, Leslie, (1), May 23, 1942; 2
- McIver, Charles O., (1), June 28, 1906; 2
- McIvor, John W., (1), Nov. 13, 1929; 2
- McNeil, J. C., (15), Jan. 30, Apr. 10, 28, Aug. 26, Sept. 30, Oct. 22, 1905, Nov. 15, 1905, July 19, 1906, 7 N.D.; 2
- McReynolds, J. C., (1), Sept. 1, 1914; 2
- Marsh, Edward C., (2), Nov. 24, Dec. 3, 1915; 2
- Matthews, Shailer, (2), Mar. 7, 1903, May 20, 1926; 2
- Maxon, James M., (1), Dec. 31, 1940; 2
- Mayhew, George N., (1), May 27, 1942; 2
- Merritt, B. O., (1), Dec. 30, 1940; 2
- Merritt, Mrs. B. O., (2), May 26, 1940, N.D.; 2
- Miller, Alice D., (1), June 29, 1926; 2
- Millikan, R. R., (6), Jan. 11, 1927, Nov. 11, 1929, Nov. 28, 1933, Oct. 31, 1941, May 11, 1950; 2
- Milton, George F., (3), Sept. 9, 1926, Oct. 28, Nov. 29, 1926; 2
- Mitchell, S.C., (2), Apr. 27, 1907, Dec. 4, 1908; 2
- Mooney, C. P., (3), May 27, 1926, June 11, 24, Sept. 4, 1926; 2
- Moore, Ernest, (1), Jan. 26, 1941; 2
- More, Paul E., (5), Nov. 10, 1905, Jan. 30, Apr. 10, 1906, Oct. 26, 1908, Jan. 8, 1930; 2
- Morgan, Hugh J., (1), Feb. 5, 1940; 2
- Morgan, John T., (1), May 3, 1905
- Mims, Andrew Jackson (1), n.d. (frag.)
- Morse, Josiah, (1), Sept. 1, 1926; 2
- Morton, A. H., (1), Jan. 31, 1940; 2
- Moss. W. P., (1), May 21, 1942; 2
- Moton, R. R., (1), Apr. 13, 1927; 2
- Mumford, Lewis, (1), Dec. 26, 1929; 2
- Munford, Mary C. B., (Mrs. Beverly B.), (1), Aug. 5, 1926; 2
- Munro, Dana C., (1), Dec. 12, 1929; 2
- Munro, William B., (1), Aug. 25, 1927; 2
- Murphy, Edgar Gardner, (5), Mar. 9, 13, 1905, Mar. 14, 1906, June 25, Aug. 21, 1908; 2
- Murray, John, (1), Dec. 20, 1936; 2
- Myers, Robert Manson, (1), May 25, 1942; 2
- Nagel, Charles, (2), Apr. 10, 1939, Apr. 13, 1942; 2
- Neblett, J. W. Family (1); (1 telegram), N.D.; 2
- Neilson, W. A., (1), Apr. 28, 1912; 2
- Nevinson, Henry W., (1), Jan. 11, 1937; 2
- Nock, Albert Jay, (3), Feb. 3, 14, 1932, Jan. 24, 1938; 2
- Nooe, Roger T., (1), June 2, 1942; 2
- Norwood Kate Anderson (Mrs. Hal), (1), Jan. 10, 1952; 2
- Noyes, Arthur A., (1), Dec. 16, 1929; 2
- Ogden, Robert C., (8), May 23, 1903, Jan. 31, Feb. 5, Mar. 30, May 28, 31, June 26, July 10, 1906; 2
- Overman, Lee S., (1), Dec. 22, 1906; 2
- Page, Arthur W., (10), Aug. 21, Nov. 13, 1911, Feb. 17, 1912, Apr. 1, May 12, 14, June 18, Sept. 27, 1926, June 11, 1957, Jan. 26, 1959; 2
- Page Curtis Hidden, (4), July, 11, Sept. 20, Nov. 14, Dec. 5, 1905; 2
- Page, Mrs. John, (1), Mar. 2, 1901; 2
- Page, Thomas Nelson, (6), Jan. 18, Mar. 13, 19, 1900, Oct. 24, Dec. 12, 1906, Nov. 22, 1907; 2
- Page, Walter H., (69) (1 card), June 11, 1902, Aug. 13, Sept. 26, 1903, N.D., N.D., N.D., Jan. 5, June 29, 1904, Aug. 22, Sept. 21, Oct. 13, 1905, Jan. 1, Sept. 29, Dec. 12, 1906, Jan. 14, Feb. 13, Mar. 15, 22, May 14, Nov. 30, Dec. 27, 31, 1907, Jan. 6, May 21, 1908, May 5, 1909, Dec. 29, 1910, Jan. 3, 5, Feb. 6, Apr. 6, 12, 14, May 4, 10, 15, 31, June, 20, Aug. 9, 12, 15, 20(c), 21, 26, Sept. 22, 30, Oct. 6, 23, Nov. 1, 8, 13, Dec. 22, 1911, Jan. 4, 10, 22, 28, Apr. 16, 26, 27, June 6, 27, July 29, Dec. 16, 1912, Apr. 5, N.D., N. D., 1913 2
- Parker, Franklin N., (1), Jan. 7, 1952 2
- Parker, W. B., (3), July 23, 1903, May 11, July 27, 1904; 2
- Parkin, George R., (1), Feb. ?, 1909; 2
- Farrington, Vernon L., (1), Mar. 13, 1929; 2
- Parrott, T. M., (1), Mar. 25, 1905; 2
- Parsons, Barbara Morris, (1), May 25, 1942; 2
- Paschall, John, (1), May 21, 1926; 2
- Payne, Bruce, (18), N.D., Aug. 14, 1905, Mar. 14, Aug. 27, Dec. 24, 1907, Jan. 15, Mar. 31, 1909, Dec. 31, 1910, Jan. 23, Mar. 10, 1911, Jan. 2, Feb. 24, Aug. 26, 1912, Mar. 10, Nov. 21, 1913, Apr. 13, 1915, Aug. 13, 1929, N.D.; 2
- Peabody, Francis G., (1), Dec. 6, 1929; 2
- Pearson, James Larkin, (1), June 11, 1926; 2
- Perron, E. C., (1), Aug. 13, 1906; 2
- Perry, Bliss, (13), Mar. 30, June 4, Sept. 23, Dec. 10, 1903, May 16, 1905, Mar. 9, 1907, Dec. 16, 1922, Nov. 5, 1929, Feb. 17, 1935, Oct. 18, 1941, Jan. 15, 1947, N.D.; 2
- Phelps, William Lyon, (2), Sept. 25, 1902, Dec. 2, 1929; 2
- Phenix, George P., (1), Jan. 26, 1927; 2
- Phillips, H. C., (1), Feb. 24, 1909; 2
- Pipkin, Charles W., (1), N.D.; 2
- Pitkin, Walter B., (2), May 10, Dec. 17, 1928; 2
- Poe, C. H., (8), Nov. 24, 1903, Feb. 7, 1905, June 21, 1906, Nov. 21, 1908, May 13, June 8, Dec. 22, 1929, N.D.; 2
- Pomfret, John E., (1), Nov. 7, 1946; 2
- Poteat, William Louis, (2), Sept. 6, 1926, Jan. 7, 1927; 2
- Pritchett, Henry S., (1), Apr. 30, 1908; 2
- Rand, F. C., (5), Oct. 23, Nov. 14, 1929, Dec. 17, 23, 1940, Jan. 27' 1941; 3
- Reed, John C., (2), Nov. 18, Dec. 20, 1905; 3
- Reinke, E. E., (1), May 25, 1942; 3
- Rice, Cale Young, (1), May 20, 1926; 3
- Rives, George E., (4), June 19, 1908, Jan. 7, 12, 13, 1909; 3
- Robinson, Canby, (1), Aug. 2, 1926; 3
- Rockefeller, John D., (3), Jan. 7, 1937, Apr. 27, 1951, May 14, 1956; 3
- Rodgers, Woodall, (1), Mar. 18, 1940; 3
- Rollins, Mrs. E. J., (1), Apr. 6, 1942; 3
- Roman, C. N., (2), May 18, 28, 1926; 3
- Roosevelt, Theodore, (1), Jan. 4, 1906; 3
- Rosenwald, Julius, (1), Aug. 26, 1926; 3
- Rowlett, Robert, (1), May 25, 1932; 3
- Rusk, Dean, (1), Mar. 26, 1956; 3
- Rutledge, Archibald, (1), undated; 3
- Sams, Stanhope, (2), Aug. 31, 1907, May 21, 1926; 3
- Scott, Frank W., (2), June 11, 1928, Feb. 2, 1929; 3
- Scribners, Charles and Sons, (2), Feb. 1, 1904, Feb. 3, 1905; 3
- Sharmon, Edgar F., (1), Mar. 16, 1914; 3
- Shaw, Albert, (10), Sept. 15, 1903, Apr. 17, 1905, June 2, 13, 25, 1907, June 2, 1925, Feb. 16, 1927, Feb. 13, 1930, Jan. 31, 1946; 3
- Sherman, Stuart, (1), June 7, 1926; 3
- Simpson, R. H., (1), Oct. 23, 1924; 3
- Sims, Cecil, (1), June 28, 1940; 3
- Sisson, Charles, (1), May 20, 1950; 3
- Sledd, Benjamin, (5), Apr. 29, 1904, July 9, 1906, Feb. 21, Mar. 6, 1912, 1 undated; 3
- Sloan, George A., (1), Jan. 20, 1941; 3
- Slosson, Edwin E., (1), Aug. 19, 1926; 3
- Small, John, (1), July 17, 1911; 3
- Smith, C. Alphonso, (3), Jan. 28, 1905, May 31, Sept. 12, 1907; 3
- Smith, Charles F., (12) (2 cards), July 23, 1893, Nov. 16, 1B94, Feb. 13, Nov. 1, 1896, Sept. 10, 1900, Feb. 15,(c), Mar. 1, 11,(c), July 17, 1903, Nov. 19, 1905, Mar. 17, 1907, Dec. 16, 1911, Mar. 17, 1912, May 18, 1913; 3
- Smith, Francis H., (3), July 22, Nov. 1, 1907, Apr. 27, 1909; 3
- Smith, Roy L., (1), Aug. 7, 1941; 3
- Snyder, Henry N., (9), Jan. 31, 1905, July 15, 1906, Mar. 7, 1912, May 13, 1913, May 19, 20, 1914, June 21, 1926, Dec. 19, 1929, Jan. 7, 1941; 3
- Southgate, J. H., (1), July 12, 1909; 3
- Spaeth, J. Duncan, (2), Oct. 9, 1931, Oct. 7, 1932; 3
- Stamp, Josiah, (5), Sept. 24, Oct. 5, Dec 7, 1937, Mar. 17, Apr. 12, 1938; 3
- Stephens, George, (3), May 27, Aug. 5, Oct. 30, 1926; 3
- Stern, Alfred K., (1), May 23, 1927; 3
- Stevenson, Alec B., (1), May 13, 1942; 3
- Stowe, Beecher, (6), May 24, June 16, Aug. 30, Sept. 8, 1926 Jan. 7, Mar. 2, 1927; 3
- Stribling, T. S., (2), Dec. 15, 1926, Jan. 3, 1927; 3
- Strother, French, (2), June 6, 25, 1926; 3
- Stuart, Jesse, (5), Aug. 24, 1951, Dec. 23, 1957, Sept. 11, Oct. 1, 1958, 1 undated; 3
- Swem, E. G., (1), Apr. 29, 1943; 3
- Swiggart, Will H., (1), June 2, 1942; 3
- Tabb, John B., (1), Mar. 3, 1904; 3
- Taylor, Jesse, (2), Dec. 27, 1940, May 19, 1942; 3
- Tead, Ordway, (1), Apr. 10, 1952; 3
- Tegarden, J. B., (1):, Oct. 11, 1926; 3
- Thorndike, A. H., (3), Jan. 16, 28, 1911, June 29, 1926; 3
- Thwing, Charles F., (1), Nov. 30, 1929; 3
- Tigert, John J., (1), Jan. 6, 1941; 3
- Tillit, W., (1), Nov. 25, 1903; 3
- Trent, W. P., (6), Dec. 15, 1899, Jan. 3, 1900, Mar. 1, June 21, 1902, May 2, July 1, 1903; 3
- Turnbull, Frances, (1), Nov. 16, 1905; 3
- Turnbull, Lawrence, (1), undated; 3
- Underwood, E. Marvin, (1), Dec. 19, 1929;3
- Underwood, S. B., (1), Apr. 18, 1909; 3
- Van Doren, Rita, (1), Sept. 7, 1926; 3
- Van Dyke, Henry, (33), Nov. 28, 1901, Apr. 28, May 6, 9, 13, 26, 1902, Jan. 14, 1903, May 5, Oct. 5, Dec. 2, 1903, Mar. 10, June 8, 15, 1904, Dec. 4, 28, 1904, May 1, 16, Nov. 3, 23, 1905, Jan. 30, May 10, 1906, Oct. 21, Nov. 28, 1907, June 25, July 2, 1908, Dec. 16, 1909, Oct. 20, 1910, July 21, 1913, Jan. 15, 1918, Oct. 23, 1923, Oct. 11, 1924, May 21, 1926, Nov. 27, 1929; 3
- Venable, F. P., (4), Jan. 26, 1906, Mar. 25, 26, 30, 1909; 3
- Villard, Oswald Garrison, (9), May 19, Oct. 19, Nov. 18, 1903, Feb. 23, 1904, Dec. 5, 1905, Apr. 9, 1906, May 1, 1907, Mar. 11, 1912, Dec. 14, 1937; 3
- Vincent, George E., (1), June 14, 1926; 3
- Walpole, Hugh, (1), Sept. 14, 1934; 3
- Ward, Susan Hayes, (1), Nov. 9, 1905; 3
- Washington, Booker T., (3), Aug. 3, 1903, May 12, 1906, June 10, 1911; 3
- Webb, John M., (8), Nov. 23, 1903, Mar. 15, Apr. 12, Dec. 25, 1907, Jan. 1, Mar. 22, 1911, Feb. 22, 1912, 1 undated; 3
- Werthan, Mary Jane Lowenstein, (1), May 25, 1942; 3
- Wheelock, John Hall, (1), Aug. 21, 1928; 3